The kettle and the idol
Now then, let's go to the main YouTube project here.
Please make a cute title call.
My three main elements
Yay
Yay!
I am going to ask you about the three most important elements to know about Ira.
Please announce them.
Here are my three major elements.
There you go!
May I start with the first one?
Food.
And the second one.
Dance.
The third is music.
I see. Food, dance, and music.
Q. What food do you recommend?
I really love to eat.
I really love it.
I am attracted to all-you-can-eat places.
Do you go to all-you-can-eat?
I go to all-you-can-eat places a lot.
I go to shabu-shabu, yakiniku, and sushi.
So you like to eat, and you eat a lot?
I eat a lot.
That's right.
I eat more in quantity.
I eat the same thing all the time.
You can eat the same thing all the time.
I like white rice.
I love white rice.
I can eat just white rice without sprinkles.
Without any side dish.
That's amazing.
Do your fans know that?
I think those who know do know.
Like ramen.
It's not so much that I like sweets,
It's more like carbohydrates.
I thought it's more like sweet sweets.
That's what I thought,
You can go all out.
Yes, I can go all out.
I make new ramen at night,
I want to arrange it and eat it by myself.
I'd like to do some arranging.
Arrangements?
What is your recommendation for new ramen?
I recommend that you make regular ramen and put egg, cheese, rice cake, bean sprouts, and hubs inside,
I recommend that you make regular ramen and put egg, cheese, rice cake, bean sprouts, and hubs in it.
This is...
I still wouldn't do that. That's amazing.
I see.
In the center.
I'd love to. But it's coming in the middle of the night?
Yes, it is. We'll start the screen around 2 am.
Really?
That's right.
Lately, a little bit,
But I'm careful.
Lately.
I have to be careful.
I have to be careful, so I am careful,
At one time, I did it every day.
No kidding.
It's true.
That's how much you eat?
Do you show this to your audience in your own distribution?
Do you arrange it in that way?
I haven't done it yet.
I did make an omu-rice on TV.
Oh? Are you going to make it?
Yes, I am. I love making omu-rice.
Oh, you do?
On a TV program. Cooking delivery.
What kind of omu-rice do you make?
When you say "omu-rice," do you have any particular image of what you mean by "omu-rice"?
I never put onions in it.
I don't like to cut onions.
I don't like to cut them.
What's that?
I never put onions in my omelet, not because of the taste, but because I don't like to cut them.
I also use bacon instead of chicken.
Bacon instead of chicken?
Bacon. I call it chicken rice,
I call it bacon rice.
Bacon rice?
That's a commitment.
That's a stickler.
Ah.
I also put eggs in the cheese to make it a little more tender.
No, it's good.
It's the best.
Eh. I wish I could show you that much.
Yes, I do.
Aira Cooking.
Aira Cooking is a cooking dish that is good for the cook, but also good for the eater.
It's totally fine.
I see. Thank you very much.
The first use of making Aira-san was for food.
It was food.
I try to make funny faces and stuff.
Ah, well, that's good there.
This program is,
Missy.
Take-chan
Mr. Hiroki
Mr. Domas
This program was presented courtesy of Missin-san.
Thank you all for watching.
Thank you very much.